My gosh, the weather is great.
The weather is amazing. It's pretty cool too.
- It was a long trip.
- Right.
I'm coming to Cheonan often these days.
When were you here again?
I came here to film "Running Man."
I came here often.
(The two MCs are chatting on the mat.)
- The weather is amazing.
- Right, it is.
- Yes.
We have some great weather today. Look at the sky too.
- Totally.
- Yes.
(Whenever Friends are joining the show on a clear autumn day.)
- They did a good job with the park.
- I...
Right? I remember coming here...
for writing contests growing up.
A lot of events were held here.
I hear that you're a year younger than Jae Seok.
He was born in 1972.
- I think they're over there.
- They're over there.
Should we sneak up on them?
There's no fine dust these days.
Who are they?
- Wait. It's Jae Myung.
- What?
- What? It's Sun Bin.
- Hello.
- What's going on?
- I'm here.
- What a surprise.
- Sun Bin.
You're finally on our show, Jae Myung.
- Nice to meet you.
- Gosh.
Hello.
(His presence blew up just by walking into the scene.)
(You guys are all dead meat.)
(It doesn't matter when or where.)
(Exuding a powerful presence)
(Restrained charisma)
(An actor who can whip up a story with just his eyes)
(Actor Yoo Jae Myung)
(Last winter, she joined them and roamed around Bongcheon-dong.)
(With her skilled body movements, )
(she easily succeeded Round 3.)
(Exploding her energy with her palm blast)
(She ended up becoming...)
(the biggest sacrificial lamb of their elementary school curse.)
(Actress Lee Sun Bin)
It's been a while, Sun Bin.
- You had no idea?
- I didn't know.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
You were on a picnic.
Please take a seat.
- Gosh. Don't mind us.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- Of course, not.
- Thank you for having us.
- Gosh.
Don't mention it.
- Jae Myung.
- Yes.
This is your first appearance on our show.
That's right. It's my first appearance.
I've only been on five variety shows.
I was on two variety shows in the beginning of my career.
- You were?
- Yes.
I recently starred on three variety shows.
- Really?
- I see.
Aren't you younger than me, Jae Myung?
- I'm a year younger.
- Right? You were born in 1973.
- I was born in 1973.
- What?
Right, in 1973.
You're from the Gangneung Yu clan, right?
That's right.
- Me too.
- Oh, my.
- Myogeumdo.
- That's right.
(Brothers from the same clan)
- Who knew someone from my clan...
- Wait.
- You know?
- I see.
- It might make you uncomfortable.
- A junior from his clan...
My junior.
- From the clan.
- It's all right.
We came all the way down to Cheonan. Who has ties...
This is my hometown.
- Sun Bin?
- No wonder.
I'm also an honorary ambassador of Cheonan.
You're the Daughter of Cheonan?
I'm the honorary ambassador of Cheonan...
and South Chungcheong Province at the same time.
- No wonder.
- Really?
- I was wondering why we were here.
- Yes.
We're at Cheonan Three-way Intersection Park.
- I have...
a lot of memories about this park.
- It's a beautiful park.
- Around...
Right. The middle school I went to is close to the park.
- I see.
- Yes.
It's nearby.
- I love Cheonan.
- This will be comfortable.
Well, we have to mention the famous walnut cakes.
People have been using walnuts to tease me all my life.
- Why?
- "Did you pay..."
"for your school with the money you got from cracking walnuts?"
- Stuff like that.
- Who made that joke?
Does Cheonan produce a lot of walnuts?
No. The old lady who made the first walnut cakes...
- She was from here.
- Yes.
- That's why.
- The creator was from here.
Right. And Cheonan...
- It's a transport hub.
- Cheonan is...
- a transport hub.
- Right.
- Yes.
- There's so much to see here.
Martyr Yu Gwan Sun.
The Independence Hall of Korea isn't far from the park.
There's a great Byeongcheon sundae restaurant nearby.
- There's a sundae street.
- Byeongcheon sundae.
And pears are famous in Seonghwan which isn't far from here.
(Famous landmarks and products introduced by Sun Bin)
She's indeed the honorary ambassador of Cheonan.
- She is.
- Right.
What about you, Jae Myung? Where are you from?
- I'm from Busan.
- Busan.
You can hear it in his accent.
Well, I can speak with the Seoul accent now.
- No.
- I barely have any accent. Right?
- Barely.
- Right. Barely.
No, you barely talk like a Seoulite.
Your accent is quite strong.
(It's crystal clear that he's from Busan.)
Right.
How did you end up starring on our show together?
Well, we're here to promote a movie...
which will hit the theaters on the 28th.
- I see. You filmed a film together.
- Tell us about the movie.
- It will premiere on October 28.
- Yes.
It's called "Ugly Duckling Ms. Maeng."
- "Ugly Duckling Ms. Maeng?"
- It will premiere then.
- Yes.
- "Ugly Duckling Ms. Maeng."
What is it? What kind of movie is it?
The CSAT is considered the Class Two National Secret.
Our movie centers around the people who design questions on the CSAT.
(The test writers from all over the country...)
(have arrived to design questions for the CSAT.)
(Welcome to our facility!)
(A Korean literature teacher, Maeng Bo Ram from a rural city...)
(accidentally becomes a test writer.)
(A veteran test writer, Moon Joo Yeol, )
(chairs the Korean literature committee.)
(They must stay in the dorm for 40 days...)
(with no outside contact.)
(A mission-oriented comedy film with full of chaos...)
(to design questions, free of any problems)
("Ugly Duckling Ms. Maeng," coming soon)
- It's a chaotic black comedy.
- A chaotic black comedy.
Jae Myung. Anyway, you look like a real-life test writer...
- for the CSAT.
- Yes.
- The role perfectly suits him.
- It's your vibe.
- Right. It was perfect for him.
- Actually,
we had to take the old college entrance exam.
- Right.
- I don't know much about the CSAT.
I learned about it through this movie.
- You took the CSAT, right?
- I did.
I also took the CSAT.
- The CSAT.
- Yes.
- Let's stop talking about the CSAT.
- Okay.
We're not here to take the CSAT.
- Right.
- We're in Cheonan too.
- Yes.
Students who are studying to take the CSAT this year...
might be stressed hearing about it.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Can I share some words of encouragement before we wrap up?
Sure. You can do that.
- I was getting to that.
- For the students...
- preparing to take the CSAT?
- Yes.
- Right.
- Please go ahead.
Dear teenagers who are preparing to take the CSAT this year.
You've worked so hard. You're almost at the finish line.
Keep trying to the end.
Don't catch a cold as seasons are changing.
Hang in there. You can do this!
You know what? You know exactly what to say on TV now.
"You can do this!"
He's only been on five variety shows.
Right. He said he was on only five variety shows.
That's... Okay.
- Honestly, I don't know much.
- Okay.
But I just wanted to share this message.
- That's so cool.
- This message...
- Really?
- I felt a sense of responsibility.
For the test takers.
Sure, I'm here for our movie.
But I also feel a sense of responsibility.
- After playing...
- Right.
- the test writer in the movie?
- After your role?
- After playing his role...
- They can catch up on the rest...
- after the test.
- Right.
- That's right.
- I just wanted to tell them that.
Anyway, let's check where we're going today.
Our schedule...
Where are we going? I'm really curious.
We need to check. All right.
"Kim Yoon A, Kim Ga Yoon,"
"and Lee Geon Woo."
"We're running a publishing house which was founded six months ago."
What?
"As for our publishing house,"
"we write everything by hand from the first page to the last."
- What?
- What does this mean?
- They write by hand?
- They're writing it by hand?
- What?
- By hand?
"When it's complete, we deliver it ourselves..."
- "in person."
- What?
"We'd love to tell people about our handwritten books."
"If we were to be on your show,"
"would we get more readers?"
I wonder if this publishing house sends out monthly issues...
and makes revenues that way.
I don't know.
Anyway, let's get going.
I need to look it up. Hold on.
- We must be there on time.
- We must be punctual.
We should get going.
- It's nine minutes away on foot.
- It's nearby.
We can just double time it then.
I love walnut cakes.
- Aren't they tasty?
- They're tasty.
- They taste different down here.
- They're different.
You need to get the original ones.
The original ones...
- Are they here?
- They're near Cheonan Station.
- They're the first walnut cakes.
- It's still there.
- My gosh, seriously.
She's indeed the honorary ambassador of Cheonan.
- I really grew up...
- If you want to be an ambassador,
- you must love Cheonan like her.
- She's the honorary ambassador.
- Right.
- You must care as deeply as her.
I was born here.
- I also went to school here.
- Right.
- I'm bound to love Cheonan.
- That makes sense.
Yeon Seok, you're from Seoul. Right?
I'm from Jinju, South Gyeongsang Province.
- I went to school there.
- Jinju?
- Yes.
Then I transferred to a school in Seoul.
- I see.
- Yes.
So my neighborhood was Gwangjin-gu.
That was my turf.
I'm really surprised right now.
The roads at the intersection weren't paved before.
- Really?
- They weren't paved like this.
- They weren't paved?
- No.
I have a lot of memories about this intersection.
Bus 400!
- Bus 400.
- Yes.
- Did you use to take that bus?
- Was that your commute bus?
- This bus, Bus 400...
- What is it?
- Is it making you tear up now?
- It's changed now.
- Okay.
- Back then,
it used to be a regular intra-city bus.
Just a regular intra-city bus?
That was my bus when I was in middle school.
And there were so many incidents...
on Bus 400 every single day.
- Why?
- What incidents?
There were a lot of scary bullies.
Yes, there were school bullies.
Those were the wild days.
- The wild era.
- Yes.
People fought for the seats...
- in the back.
- Yes. That was a thing too.
I used to take Bus 400 to go to school.
It was crazy.
My stories can't air on TV.
As soon as you saw Bus 400, you remembered the old days.
- More like a trauma.
- The trauma came back.
- I see.
- It was a trauma.
- Yes. It wasn't easy.
- OB versus YB?
- We're the young team.
- Hold on.
- Cheonan Dong Middle School.
Cheonan Dong Middle School. That's my alma mater.
- You went there?
- Yes, Cheonan Dong Middle School.
Back then, it was an all-girls' school.
But after I graduated, it became a co-ed school.
It was so unfair.
Hey, that's the place.
- Where?
- What?
- It's the middle school?
- We're going to her alma mater.
We're going to my school?
- Really?
- It's the school.
- I'm about to throw up. Wait.
- That's the location.
- I'm so nervous.
- How long has it been for you?
- It was a publishing house.
- Right.
- Wait. Last year...
- But the location-wise...
It could be the school magazine.
- Is it something like that?
- Really?
- That could be it.
- No way.
- I don't think so.
- Are students still in school?
- It can't be the school.
- They're still in school now.
- Right.
- Of course, they'll be there.
- It's Thursday.
- No way.
But we can't enter a school. Can we?
It's the school. That's the address.
(Checking the map)
- It's the school.
- The school!
- No way.
How...
(According to the map, it's the school.)
Gosh, so much has changed.
- There was no cover before.
- I see.
The road wasn't painted green on the hill over there.
- Why are schools on a hill?
- They're all on a hill. Right.
I guess we're really going there!
All the schools are on a hill.
My calves are still sore...
- from the hills.
- Right.
Right.
I'm suddenly getting sweaty all over my body.
(I can't believe I'm going to my school.)
Visiting your alma mater...
- I don't personally love that.
- Gosh.
- I have no good memories about it.
- You don't like it either.
- Why not?
- We were often beaten in school.
Same here. I got beaten a lot too.
- This is crazy.
- It's a bit embarrassing too.
I can't believe I'm here.
No way.
Gosh, unbelievable.
The discipline committee...
- would be guarding the gate.
- Right.
They always taught us a lesson.
- You know?
- Their effort to send students...
- Going to school late...
- Right.
- No way.
- Looking back, we came across...
as potential troublemakers.
- My gosh.
- There were some troublemakers.
If I were to go back,
- that would be normal.
- Being late to school was huge.
- Exactly.
- It's hillier than I expected.
The hill was no joke.
The road wasn't paved like this.
There was a school supply store. But it's gone.
- I can already hear them.
- Hey.
- The students are here.
- Already...
- I can already hear them.
- No way.
(Walking up the hill that's full of Sun Bin's old memories...)
This is so surreal. I can't believe this.
- They're welcoming us.
- No.
- It's for Jae Seok.
- They're all cheering for us.
(Waving at them too)
- No way.
- It's like they're cheering for me.
- Right?
- Are they cheering for you?
(Feeling happy)
(Entering the school while feeling like superstars)
- My armpits are sweaty.
- Are you nervous?
- This is your alma mater, right?
- That's right.
This is my school.
Exactly. I bet you were nervous to come to school back then.
(Dazed)
(It feels even more surreal to be in school.)
I can't believe this.
You're their senior.
(Back at the place where her school memories are alive)
- Hold on. The math room.
- Right here.
The math room. It's right here.
(They'll soon meet their first Whenever Guests.)
- They're here.
- The students are here.
- Hello.
Which one of you wrote to our show?
- Ga Yoon. There are three of you.
- Yes.
- Hello.
(Whenever Guests: Kim Yoon A, Kim Ga Yoon, Lee Geon Woo)
Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- So cute.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Yoon A. Geon Woo. Ga Yoon.
(Chuckling)
The school uniform looks more stylish now.
- The design is different now?
- Back then...
There was no school uniform?
The school uniform looks much more stylish now.
Sun Bin graduated from this school.
Did you know that I graduated from this school?
- She's your senior.
- What year are you guys in?
- We're first-years.
- First-years in middle school?
- Yes.
- What about you?
- So they might not know.
What were you supposed to be doing now?
- It's our lunchtime.
- Lunchtime?
- I see. Lunchtime?
- It's 11:30am now.
When does your lunchtime start and end?
- It ends at 12:25pm.
It ends at 12:25pm.
In your letter, you said...
you guys made books and ran a publishing house.
- Right here. Magazines...
- We make magazines.
- I see. Every month?
- We are...
- in the school magazine club.
- I see.
- The school magazine?
- So cute!
- So it's a magazine?
- Yes.
- You guys made this yourselves?
- "Dongjung Daily."
You can find information about teachers.
- "Chuseok is around the corner."
- Every month.
(Pages are filled with their own opinions and insight)
"What do you think about watching the soccer tournament in school?"
"I'm on board." "I'm against it."
- The name of the club...
- It's also in the May issue.
"Can middle school students celebrate Children's Day?"
- To see if you guys are...
- There's...
considered young enough to celebrate it?
- Yes.
What do you think? Can they celebrate Children's Day?
In my opinion, middle schoolers are allowed to celebrate Children's Day.
Wouldn't you say that first-years are still considered...
children?
- I think...
- No?
- They can't?
- middle schoolers aren't children.
- I see.
- They should be considered...
- teenagers by this point.
- Okay.
- Right.
- Teenagers?
Kids up to elementary school age only count as children.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Up to elementary school age.
- Once they started middle school,
- they're on their own.
- Right. They must be independent.
- They're on their own?
You can ride the bus on your own.
- Right.
- You can make ramyeon too.
Even elementary school kids...
- can do them.
- Right.
That's true.
How did the vote go?
The side in favor of celebrating the day received a lot more votes.
- So we can celebrate the day.
- We can celebrate Children's Day.
- You can celebrate it.
- Up to middle school?
- I see.
- Six-sevenths voted in favor of it.
Kids might criticize me for saying this.
Even sixth graders...
(They can't be considered children.)
Jae Seok.
- They can still celebrate it.
- Even sixth graders?
Jae Seok, there might be a major backlash...
- when they watch this episode.
- Right. The kids?
That's why I said earlier...
- Up to...
- Ten-year-olds are...
pretty much all grown up.
- Ten-year-olds?
- Ten-year-olds.
(This guy is worse.)
Please don't get the wrong idea.
It's just a personal opinion of ours.
Right.
What does this publishing club do?
On top of publishing the school magazine,
what else does the club do?
We gather news ourselves.
- We edit the stories...
- You edit the stories.
And print them out.
- You must be busy, though.
- Right.
You have to attend classes, do homework, and go to academies.
We try to get our work done during our breaks.
Hold on. You were holding onto this notebook.
What's this?
That's where I keep all of my interview notes.
- It's her journalism notebook.
- Her journalism notebook.
- Can I show this to them?
- Yes.
- It's her journalism notebook.
- Her journalism notebook.
(It includes activity records and interview notes.)
That's why you wrote everything by hand.
(Pages filled with handwritten notes)
- That's how...
- You interviewed your classmates.
- Right.
- That's interesting.
I assumed kids these days did everything on their phone.
- Right. By hand.
- She wrote everything by hand.
- Really?
- She's so smart.
Yes.
Ga Yoon, how did you end up joining this publishing club?
Yoon A joined the club first.
- Yoon A joined the club first.
- This is a self-governing club.
- We founded it ourselves.
- Right.
- She asked me to join this club.
- I see.
- You guys founded the club?
- Yes.
- "Random Bits."
- I see.
How did you end up joining the club, Geon Woo?
He desperately begged me, so I made an exception for him.
Really?
The club was already full with five members.
So I couldn't join the club before. But then she said I could join.
- Why did you want to join the club?
- Right.
I like working with other students.
- Really?
- Gosh.
I like making magazines...
and distributing them.
I can hear it in your tone that you really wanted.
- So...
- I can hear his enthusiasm.
- Right.
- So...
What are your roles in this publishing club?
- Are your roles divided?
- Yes, they are.
Captain, delivery man,
- and vice-captain.
- Come again?
- She's the captain.
- He delivers the magazines.
- I'm the vice-captain.
- Delivery.
- So you deliver the magazines?
- Yes, I do.
- You deliver them?
- So you deliver the magazines...
- to each classroom?
- Yes. I give them to our teachers.
(He delivers them all over the school.)
- Like this?
- What's your role?
I'm the vice-captain. So I draw the cartoons on the back.
- These cartoons here.
- You do art and draw cartoons.
(Ga Yoon's cartoons are on the back of the magazines.)
I noticed that the division of roles like planning was printed here.
Yoon A...
- She's the editor-in-chief.
- Right.
Basically, she's their leader.
She takes on a lot of roles.
Geon Woo is listed under collaboration.
- Collaboration. He likes that.
- So he doesn't have a key role.
He hasn't established himself yet.
Wait. His name is under news gathering.
- News gathering. Yes, it is.
- His name is under that too.
But take a look at this.
One, two, three, four, five, six. His name is the seventh one.
- It's in alphabetical order.
- It follows our individual numbers.
- It's in alphabetical order?
- Yes.
Can I share some personal feedback?
There's so much wasted space in the magazines.
- Gosh, don't say that.
- Come on, sir.
They're busy with homework and academies.
- Sir.
- Running this club is hard enough.
- Don't talk about the wasted space.
- You sounded like a real teacher.
- It's the art of blank space.
- Come on. Look.
- You sounded like a teacher.
- It looks nice.
It's all right. I think...
the quality is top-notch...
considering you put this together despite your busy schedules.
How do you pay for all this?
- Does the school help you?
- Does the school provide money?
- No, we cover it.
- We don't get any funding.
- No funding?
- Then how do you run the club?
- We just do it ourselves.
- We do it ourselves.
We received two bags of chewing candy,
so we could use them during carrying out our surveys.
- Chewing candy?
- That's it.
Chewing candy?
- Gosh, she's so cute.
- I see.
Your friends gave you two bags of chewing candy?
- No, our teachers did.
- Your teachers gave them to you.
What was the hardest thing you had to do?
The hardest thing? We had to conduct a survey...
with the older students.
They ignored us because we were too young.
That happens.
- It's like a power struggle.
- Right.
In middle school, there's a huge gap between the 1st-years and 3rd-years.
- The gap is huge. Right.
- Gosh, there's a huge gap.
There's a huge difference.
And they look a bit scary to us.
- Right.
- I see.
Here's what we need to remember. In the beginning of the year,
they had just started middle school after graduating...
- from elementary school. Right.
- Exactly.
That's why when we had to deliver the magazines to their classrooms,
- we were so scared.
- You were scared?
We put them on the podium and left the classroom quickly.
- I see.
- We delivered them in two seconds.
(Finding them adorable)
You gave up?
What made you write to our show?
(Turning toward the Whenever Guest)
I was just watching TV...
on the weekend with my parents.
They thought that I would make...
a lot of fun memories with my friends on this show.
That's why I wrote the letter.
What a sweet answer.
Because it would be a chance to make fun memories.
How did your friends react when you said you guys were chosen?
- They thanked me.
- They thanked you?
I even danced.
- You danced?
- How did you dance?
Like this.
(Hula dancing)
So cute.
It's the Shin Chan Dance.
(Adoring her)
I noticed that...
young kids these days film a lot of challenge videos...
- with their friends.
- Right.
Right? Don't you guys film a lot of challenge videos?
- I don't have a cell phone.
- You don't?
- No.
- Really?
- What about you, Geon Woo?
- I have one.
- Ga Yoon?
- I have one too.
- You do? How come...
- Yes.
- you don't have one, Yoon A?
- Why...
My parents said that they'd buy me one when I grew up.
- That's so cool.
- It's amazing that...
she didn't ask for one...
- when they said she'd get it later.
- Right.
She could've pestered them for one.
- Kids would usually ask for one.
- Right.
That's been the topic of my family discussion these days.
- When to buy a phone for your kid?
- When to buy one for my son.
We've been discussing that.
Are there any inconveniences from not having a phone?
No, I'm actually enjoying my life.
(Deeply moved)
- That's so cool.
- I can't believe this.
That's really cool.
- Right now...
- It's so cool.
She's indeed the captain.
- She's my junior.
- The captain.
- That's impressive.
- She's my junior.
- For your next issue...
- You know what?
You guys should let me be...
- in the November issue.
- Right. Interview her.
Yes.
You can take pictures of me.
Anyway, we're going to play games for the three of them today.
- This is your alma mater, Sun Bin.
- Right.
We ought to give out some presents to them.
- Sounds good. We must.
- Let's make good memories for them.
They're getting presents no matter what.
Crack it and check the prize for Round One.
I hope it's a good one.
- Please.
- A good one?
"It's a treat from Random Bits."
"A snack bar just for Class 1-7."
"The ultimate snack set."
That's awesome.
(Clapping)
Really?
(The prize for Round 1 is brought in.)
(Covering his mouth)
They're bringing in an entire convenience store.
- My gosh.
- Goodness. Hold on.
(There are two?)
- This is great.
- There are three shelves?
- Gosh.
- I...
- This is great.
- There are three shelves?
(Blushing)
- Hey, this is...
- We have to succeed now.
We won't have to starve for ten years.
My goodness.
- Sun Bin.
- My goodness.
- I'm suddenly feeling the pressure.
- Yes?
- Right? This is what happens.
- I see it now.
This is what happens.
- I love it.
- I also want the shelves.
They're here.
(Spotting some people)
Their friends...
Hello.
- Hello.
- Look at the snacks.
The prize for Round One.
- What if they fail Round 1?
- Round 1?
Guys, don't be so disappointed if we don't get to succeed.
- We won't be!
- You look so pretty.
Thank you.
That's one prize?
(The fangirl is happy.)
Let's succeed today.
All right. What do we need to do?
(There Goes the Plane)
(Use 10 paper airplanes...)
(to complete the bingo with the milk crates.)
(Round 1: Complete 1 line of bingo.)
(The starting line)
(9 milk crates)
(They must fly paper planes toward the crates...)
(and complete one line of bingo.)
(Time limit: 30 seconds)
- The milk crates?
- Complete a line of bingo?
(The milk crate trauma)
This won't be easy.
We need to practice.
(They begin practicing.)
That's great.
- We need to practice.
- That's great.
That's too...
The direction will play an important role.
I should make the wings big.
This one is hard.
- Right. It's not working.
- It's not flying as we expected.
Getting the paper plane in the milk crate we want...
- isn't easy.
- Right.
This isn't easy.
If we fail...
Our goal is to complete a line of bingo. That's it.
(Going in)
You got it.
(His paper plane is flying straight.)
He did it.
This...
Gosh, it went in again.
That's great. We need to get it to fly into the box.
Yes, this is the best method.
Okay.
You can throw it slightly faster.
There you go.
That was excellent.
It went right in.
- We should throw it faster.
- Make sure it goes in right away.
- Make it go in right away.
That was good.
(I got the hang of it now.)
- Gosh.
- We got it.
It's going to work. We'll get to take the prize.
Let's give it a try.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
You should take three.
- Three?
- Take three.
- I don't want to take a lot.
- You also take three.
- Three?
- Sun Bin will take three.
- Take three.
- Okay.
- We'll take 2 each.
- Great.
- Oh, please.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Ready.
- All right. Ready.
- How will we complete a line?
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
- This won't be easy.
- Set.
- It won't be easy.
- You got it!
- You have to get one in the crate.
- Okay.
It doesn't matter where.
- Darn it.
- We need one in the crate, Sun Bin.
- You got it. That's great.
- Great!
- Great! Then...
- Okay.
Wait.
You got it!
- You got it! Gosh.
- My gosh.
(1st try)
- You got it.
- Okay. Over there!
- Yes!
- The top row!
- Jae Seok.
- Okay. Over there!
- All right.
- The top row!
- Jae Seok. Fly it higher.
- Okay. Over there!
- All right.
- Right.
- Over there!
- The top row!
- Jae Seok. Fly it higher.
- Darn it.
- Ten seconds left!
The top row.
- Ten seconds. No!
- Gosh.
- The top row. Ten seconds.
(It flies through the hole.)
- I think you can do this.
- Five,
- Five.
- four...
- No.
- It's the last one.
- Two...
(They only have 1 plane left.)
- Three...
- It's the last one.
(They fail.)
We were so close.
Come on. Why didn't that fly up properly?
My goodness. It didn't go well this time.
- Gosh, we were so close.
- Right, we were.
- My goodness. This is...
- We definitely need that.
I'd love to put some magnets on the crates.
- Let's try one more time.
- Shall we?
- Let's try this.
- Let's get our energy up.
- All right.
- We can do this.
Will I go first again?
Yes.
All right.
I'm feeling a lot of pressure as the last player.
That's the pressure.
- He starts counting down.
- Right.
- Then you can go 2nd.
- I'll go 2nd.
- Can I donate one of my planes?
- Sure.
- You were pretty good earlier.
- Sure. Okay.
- Two, three, three, and two.
- Gosh, this is...
- This is a tough position.
It's not easy.
- Going last...
- All right. Let's go!
- Let's go!
Ready. It's your second try.
Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
- Set.
- We might run out of time.
(2nd try)
- Darn it.
- It's okay.
- It has to go in.
- One has to go in.
- It's okay.
- That's nice.
- It's okay. Darn it.
- Nice.
Nice.
Yes!
- Gosh, this is...
- Get the center crate.
(It lands in the same crate.)
- Which one are we going with?
- Darn it.
- Darn it. Hold on.
- Which one are we going with?
- Which one?
- Hold on.
- We got it.
- The bottom crate!
- I got one.
- The last one.
- The bottom left crate?
- We got it.
- The last one.
(Please get one more crate!)
- We got it.
- The bottom crate!
- The last one.
- The bottom left crate?
- We got it. The last one.
The bottom left crate?
All the way at the bottom!
(There's a higher chance of success now.)
- All the way at the bottom!
- The top crate. You have options.
- Ten seconds!
- You can do this.
- It's okay.
It's okay.
(Yeon Seok is the only one left.)
- The top crate. You have options.
- It's okay.
- It's okay. We did it!
- Yes!
(Bingo!)
- We did it!
- Yes!
(Yeon Seok finishes a line!)
Yes!
(Cheering)
We did it!
- We love you! Yes!
- My gosh!
Round One, success!
I served in the Air Force!
- Great job.
- I served in the Air Force.
- Planes.
- Gosh.
- He's mentioning that again.
- The angle was great.
I'm from the 630th Class of the Air Force.
- He's mentioning that again.
- Right. It's about planes.
- Great job.
- No wonder!
All right. Round One,
- success.
- Success.
- You have a decision to make now.
- I'm sweating.
Do you want to keep going or stop here?
Should we keep going?
- Let's do it. We must go for it.
- Go.
- Go?
- One, two, three.
- Go!
- My gosh.
- Wait.
Isn't this enough, kids?
(Increased pressure)
Why don't you crack the second one, Yoon A?
(What's the prize for Round 2?)
Within two tries...
"To get inspired with brilliant stories and write articles,"
"we need cultural experience."
"It's 500 dollars' worth of gift vouchers."
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
(Round 2 present: 500 dollars' worth of gift vouchers)
That's great. It's 500 dollars.
Random Bits don't get any funding.
The gift vouchers will come in handy.
Not feeling the pressure is impossible.
- Right. It's just impossible.
- Yes.
(Round 2: Complete 2 lines of bingo.)
- That's tough.
- Two lines?
- That's way too hard.
- It sounds tough.
They won't give us more paper planes, right?
Come on.
(Pouting)
Then we must get the center crate no matter what.
- Right.
- Yes.
That way, we can complete more lines efficiently...
- with different directions.
- Yes.
That way, we won't need a lot of tries.
Whoever goes first...
At least two of their planes must go into the crates.
Right. Whoever goes first should do that.
It doesn't matter which crate it is. Whoever goes first...
- Right?
- must get two crates like this.
This is tough.
(Getting 2 consecutive planes into the crates)
(3 planes in a row)
That's it.
Right? This looks good.
(3 planes in a row)
(4 planes in a row)
- Great.
- That went in nicely.
He's always good during practice.
Sorry?
- Sorry?
- It's nothing.
You must've watched our show.
It's not easy.
How do I reach out the farthest?
- Watch me. Stretch your body out...
- Yes?
- as much as you can.
- I might fall.
Give it a flick.
A flick.
That's it.
- Nice.
- Great.
We've got it. Let's do it.
(Sun Bin scores a goal.)
(Yeon Seok and Jae Myung score a goal.)
(They've gotten the hang of it!)
- Let's go for it.
- Flick it lightly.
- Let's try right away.
- Okay.
Let's try.
Let's do a group cheer.
(Fine-tuning the plane)
We're on a roll right now.
- We've got a former Air Force guy.
- Right.
- As a former Air Force...
- A former Air Force...
- is different.
- Exactly.
But I've never flown a plane.
(No experience flying a plane)
- Let's...
- Stay calm.
- Let's do this.
- Good luck!
- Stay calm.
Here we go!
It's the third try.
Ready.
Set.
(3rd try)
- Lower it slightly.
- Get it in.
Get one in.
(Suddenly, controlling is a struggle.)
- Oh, no. Why are you going there?
- It's going to the side.
- Oh, dear. It's...
- It's flying to the side.
- Throw it higher.
- Okay.
- That's it.
- We have hope.
I should've gotten one in.
(Same-spot finish)
This is tough.
Air Force!
(2 planes remain.)
(Air Force Yeon Seok must succeed.)
(3rd try)
Wait. How did I do it?
I'd better use a new plane.
The whistle...
Even the whistle sounds pathetic.
The whistle is getting more and more...
It's like it's teasing us.
"Whatever."
Guys, we need you two...
to get some planes in.
- Go first, Yeon Seok.
- Me?
You have to get some in.
- Why does it fly to the side?
- I know, right?
- Let's try right away.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- Tries 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- We do.
- We have six tries.
- It'll be okay.
We can do it.
- Totally.
- Three, three, two, two?
- Yes.
- I'm going to score...
no matter what.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
(5th try)
Nice.
- Doesn't that count?
- No.
Well done.
- Good.
- I've got one left.
- Let's try together.
- Nice.
- Well done.
- Get the right corner.
- Gosh.
- Why would you fly over there?
- Take it slow.
Get it in any box.
- That's it.
- Yes. One box left.
(Get it in the target spot to complete 2 lines of bingo.)
- That's it.
- Yes. One box left.
(Screaming)
(Sun Bin is 3rd with 2 planes.)
That one box.
- There.
- Fly it higher.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- The top or bottom box.
(A higher chance of success)
- Hold on.
- The top or bottom box.
(5th try)
It's in!
(They made a full 3-line bingo.)
(Screaming)
The bottom one.
- We succeeded.
- Get it in any box.
- Did we succeed?
(The joy of success finally kicks in.)
- We succeeded.
We succeeded!
We succeeded.
(Laughing)
(Jumping)
Nice!
(Secured the Round 1 snack set and Round 2 gift voucher)
We succeeded! Here!
- Awesome.
- We succeeded.
- It wasn't easy.
- No, right?
(Patting the snacks)
- One, two, three. We got three.
- Success!
- Three bingos.
- We got three bingos.
- We got three.
- Three.
We got three bingos.
(Round 2, success)
Amazing.
We had that one shot.
- Nice.
- It's been a while...
- You didn't know, did you?
- I have one left.
I was told to get one more in.
- Get one more in.
- It was the perfect teamwork.
- By the way...
- Yes?
How many tries are left?
- Isn't it 5?
- Tries 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- We have...
Five tries left.
Random Bits should have a discussion first.
You do know that, right? If we fail Round Three,
- you lose...
- You take the prizes away.
All the prizes behind you.
You'll lose the snacks...
- and the 500-dollar gift voucher.
- It'd be a waste.
- Have a discussion.
- Think carefully.
Guys, we'd lose everything if they fail.
But we could get a Tesla car.
- No way.
- A Tesla car?
- Let's go for it.
- You don't even have a license.
- Round Three?
- A Tesla car?
A Tesla car in Round Three?
Geon Woo, think before you talk.
- That's cute.
- What should we do?
- Let's go for it.
- Go?
- Are you ready?
Okay. In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
- Okay.
- Think positively.
Tries 6 through 10. We have a handful of tries left.
- That's right.
- We'll give it our all.
- All right.
- Gosh.
"Eight pairs of N Brand shoes..."
- What?
- Go ahead.
"for fast reporting and speedy delivery..."
"from the 1st to 5th floor of the school."
(Round 3 present: 8 pairs of sneakers)
For everyone?
(Nice!)
- Shoes?
- Eight pairs of shoes.
The production crew brought them over.
(Sneakers to help with the intense reporting)
They brought the shoes to show them.
My gosh, these are...
The prizes are too much.
- Nice.
- We must succeed.
My gosh.
- It's pretty.
- Gosh.
- It's...
- Each one is in their size.
I won't have to worry about my foot health for a decade.
- A decade?
- Okay.
Okay. What's for Round Three?
(Round 3)
(The center square of the bingo board is blocked.)
(Complete 2 bingo lines, excluding the center.)
- What?
Then...
Two bingos. We should complete two bingos.
To score two bingos,
we have to get an upside-down L like earlier.
Yes, an upside-down L.
- Right? An upside-down L.
- It's harder now.
- Or two vertical lines.
- It was easier earlier.
- Since the center box is blocked.
- Like that.
This one is tough. It's really tough.
(They're all worried.)
(Crunching)
It's good.
- Right? It's vanilla flavor.
- And...
- It's really good.
- We have a chance left.
(Enjoying the fortune cookie)
I want more.
It's really good.
- It's seriously good.
- Right?
(Crowded in front of the fortune cookie)
The students are hungry.
It's lunchtime.
How cute.
Shall we give it a shot?
- Okay.
- Right away?
- Let's do it.
- We've got the hang of it.
It's best to keep the momentum going.
We can do it. It's all about concentration.
- It's all about concentration.
- We succeeded earlier.
- We can do it. We should focus.
- Yes.
- Concentration is everything.
- Right.
- Stay calm.
- We could be lucky...
- We can do it.
- with the center blocked.
We can do it.
In this order? Okay.
(For the health of the juniors)
Here we go.
Stay calm. Concentrate.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
(6th try)
Oh, no.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
(6th try)
Oh, no.
- Nice.
- Good.
- That was good.
- Nice.
- Why'd you fly to the side?
- Get one.
- Nice.
- Good.
- You can do it. Show your power.
- Hurry.
Nice.
Make it into an L.
(It's a success if they score 2 more boxes.)
Okay, one more.
Nice.
- The first row.
- It's still possible.
The first row.
Relax. You did it.
- You did it.
- Why there?
It's not over yet.
It's... Gosh.
(Jae Seok must get the remaining 2 planes in.)
Five, four...
(6th try)
(Failed even if he flies the last plane)
- Jae Seok.
- Just one.
Just one box.
We were short by one box.
(Missed just one box)
The center being blocked sure is difficult.
Good luck!
It's a tough one.
- The bell is ringing.
- Let's do it.
It's the warning bell.
The bell goes off again in five minutes.
Okay, let's hurry.
- Right.
- We must succeed fast.
We're short on time.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(7th try)
(Failed)
- "You get an extra try."
(They also failed at the chance round.)
If only we scored that one box.
(They moved on to the 8th try.)
(Failed)
Seriously.
- Why did those two...
- Gosh.
- We have to try right away.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- That was so close.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- We're out of time.
- Go!
- Thanks.
Go!
- Let's try right away.
- We can do it.
Let's do this.
(Cheonan Dong Middle's pilots met unexpected turbulence.)
We have to go for it right away due to the time.
Okay.
- Here we go.
- Lunch will end soon.
Please.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
I'm nervous.
Okay. Let's do this. Go.
Okay. Ready.
Please.
Set.
(9th try)
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- That was so close.
- What a bummer.
- Gosh.
- It's okay.
- Nice.
- Nice, Yeon Shik.
- It's okay.
- Nice.
- Nice!
- That's it!
Nice!
(Two landed side-by-side.)
- Oh, no.
- No, don't go in there.
Seriously?
Seriously, am I for real?
(All 3 crash-landed.)
I feel as if I've been shot.
My heart hurts so much.
- I feel as if I've been shot.
- I need to make a bingo.
(The remaining 3 planes must land inside the box to succeed.)
The three...
(They'll fail if even one doesn't go in.)
(They failed their 9th try.)
- What do we do now?
- That was so close.
- It was me.
What do we do?
(They ultimately face the final try.)
- Hey.
- It was me. I messed it up.
What do we do?
- That was so close.
- Should we do more practice?
- How depressing.
- It's not easy.
It's the last try. Let's do it.
We have to try now because the class starts soon.
Don't lose all faith in us yet.
- Okay.
Let's do a group cheer. Here, come.
The last try.
- Please.
- Here.
- The students look a little...
It's giving me PTSD.
We're out of time.
- We'll try our best.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
(Let's escape the turbulence.)
- Hurry.
- I can't watch them anymore.
- Don't look.
- No, we'll try our best to the end.
- You can do it!
- The last try.
- Or I'll cover one of my eyes.
- We believe in you.
We really believe in you.
Let's go!
(A sliver of hope still remains.)
- I have to get two in at the least.
- We can do it.
- Get two in at the least.
Being short on time is making me lose it.
It's our last try.
- Call it.
- Here we go!
The last try. Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
Set.
- That was so close.
- It bounced out.
(Last try)
Nice.
Nice. Great.
It's not easy.
Good.
(The plane got stuck in between!)
What?
(Consecutive crash landings)
- Goodness.
- You never know.
You never know with the two boxes.
(If only Jae Seok gets the remaining 2 planes into the target boxes)
(Their destiny is in the hands of Jae Seok.)
- You never know.
- Oh, no.
No, please.
(The end)
(Disappointed)
(Frustrated)
(Groaning)
Don't push me.
(They can't dare look at the students.)
(The members are desperately looking away from the students.)
(Rushing in)
Who's coming in?
They're taking the prizes away.
(Retrieving all the prizes)
- Really?
- What...
- Let's move out of the way.
- No.
- We...
- Get some.
Take some snacks.
Take a snack each. Hurry.
Can we take one each?
Grab it.
Sneak some out. Come on.
Here.
(Stealing prizes out of guilt)
(Overjoyed by the snacks)
- Take some.
- Let them have some snacks.
- Snacks.
- The students are hungry.
- Totally.
- I'd better...
put them in a frame.
(Seeing them happy makes them feel worse.)
What a bummer.
- Yoon A, I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, Ga Yoon.
- Thank you.
- We tried our best.
- Here, Tae Hoon. I'm sorry.
- These are Whenever Possible merch.
- You can't buy it from anywhere.
- Really.
- We did our best.
- This merch.
It's more meaningful than the earlier prizes.
- Thanks.
- You're totally right.
- Thank you, Geon Woo.
- I designed the hat.
I designed it myself, so you should... Aren't I right?
I'll make sure to wear it often.
- The thing is...
- Nice.
We tried our best, but it was hard. In particular...
- Being pressed for time...
made it worse.
It's time to go to class, right?
- Come here.
- Come.
- Can't we skip class?
- We're really sorry, guys.
- Line up in front of us.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Yoon A.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(A photo with the magazine club Random Bits)
- All done.
- We're sorry, guys.
- We're sorry.
- Guys, we're sorry.
- I'm sorry, Ga Yoon.
- Oh, no.
- I'm sorry.
- This is much more meaningful.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- I pray you live long.
- Bye.
- Great work.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye.
- We were terrible at it.
(Distressed)
The game was hard.
I'm heartbroken. What's more, they're my juniors.
What a letdown.
We had several golden opportunities.
Normally, don't shows...
have a comeback chance?
- This show has no mercy.
- It's...
At least we gave the students some snacks.
I'm sorry. I stole some things today.
Snacks were the least we could do.
The next spare time is 2:30pm.
- We have two hours left.
- Shall we have lunch?
- Yes, let's have lunch.
- Let's eat first.
- Despite failing, - Right.
- we're getting food.
- I'm hungry.
I have no appetite right now.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- I have a feeling you'll dig in.
- Right?
I am thirsty.
Have some water first.
(All drink water from the bottles.)
Where should we go eat, Sun Bin?
I often go downtown.
Like where downtown?
- Sinbu-dong.
- Our next spare time...
is in Sinbu-dong.
Is it in Sinbu-dong?
- Sun Bin.
- Let's go there.
It's near the bus terminal.
I'm boiling inside, so let's have something refreshing.
Let's get going.
- Don't forget your things.
- We should leave this area quickly.
I have no face to show.
Oh, dear.
My gosh. Hi.
(The students are out to see them off.)
(Bidding farewell brightly even if they failed)
She's your senior.
(The celebrity from Cheonan Dong Middle School)
- There are students up there too.
- Up there?
(Bye, Sun Bin!)
Bye.
(After bidding farewell brightly)
Let's go. Let's hurry.
I felt so ashamed while saying bye to them.
Even when saying bye to them.
I can still feel the aftermath.
But it was really...
Are games usually like that?
The games change every single time.
It's hard to bring the tension up.
- Unbelievable.
- Most of the buses go there.
- Yes, all go to the bus terminal.
- I see.
- Bus 405 is the express bus.
- Bus 405?
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Let's take that bus.
- It's much quicker.
Let's take Bus 405.
Sinbu-dong seems like the main street.
- Yes, among the others.
- Right?
But Buldang-dong,
you know the new towns in the northwest?
- It's quite the...
- I wouldn't know.
I wouldn't know.
- I thought you'd know.
- Cheonan is...
I wouldn't know Cheonan.
- Regarding Cheonan, - Yes?
We know nothing.
It's all grand and fancy...
- over there...
- Is that so?
With department stores and such.
In the past, the only downtown was near...
- the bus terminal, right?
- Correct.
There and near Cheonan Station.
(Is the bus coming?)
It's come a long way.
It's not...
That was quite a lot of energy consumption.
- You were laser focused.
- Jae Myung...
keeps saying the games are energy consuming.
(He's already drained.)
I feel foggy.
It's near downtown.
(Thinking)
Where the letter is from.
I'm asking because I don't know, but by arriving soon...
We're in South Chungcheong Province.
- That's right.
- This is...
South Chungcheong Province.
I finally get it.
- That's why, right?
- Yes.
- We've got to wait patiently.
- Right.
It's been two minutes since I've seen "arriving soon."
That's why people are chill.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Or you should've taken the earlier bus.
Yes, you're totally right.
What is it?
In Seoul, the bus would come immediately when it's arriving soon.
- It's South Chungcheong Province.
- I asked her why...
We're in Chungcheong Province.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
No wonder the people are chill.
- Is the dialect a must?
- We should've come sooner.
- It's because...
- The bus will be here soon.
We visited Incheon.
Incheon was also different...
- from Seoul.
- True.
But it can't beat Chungcheong Province.
- In Incheon, you step out...
- It's here.
Is it here?
- Is it not Bus 405?
- It's Bus 405.
- Yes, it is.
- It's here.
- Hi.
(The arriving soon bus came after 6 minutes.)
- One person will pay for everyone.
- Yes.
- Doesn't it have a vibe?
- I love...
- I love how cool it is.
- Right?
It's cooling in here.
What were we getting again?
There's a perilla oil makguksu place.
They must also have mulmakguksu.
(Mulmakguksu?)
A walnut cake shop should be near, right?
- If there's one...
- I'm sure there must be one.
It's perfect as dessert.
It's not the original, but still.
It's fine. I'm fine with anything.
Where we were was further in.
It was far away from Cheonan's downtown.
- Was it further in?
- Yes.
We're getting closer to downtown.
- When you push it...
- That's right.
This station is Cheonan Jungang Market.
Cheonan Jungang Market is near Cheonan Station.
- We're almost there.
- Are we?
Yes. It's not that far from Cheonan Station.
- It's still ten minutes away.
- Yes.
For us, locals, if it's ten minutes away...
Is it close by?
It's just a stone's throw away.
- The concept of distance...
- That's right.
Is different for them. I knew it.
- Of course.
- They're relaxed.
Gosh. Of course.
The passengers must be flustered.
But people in South Chungcheong Province...
don't let it show.
- You're right. Yes.
- They're cool like that.
- They won't let it show.
- We can only tell by their faces.
- They only murmured momentarily.
- Yes.
They must be talking on their phones...
- that we're in front of them.
- Right. It's crazy.
Right? You just told people, didn't you?
Yes.
How old are you?
- I'm 20.
- Really?
- I thought you were in high school.
- I know.
- You look so young.
- Where are you heading?
To Cheonan Station. I'm heading home after school.
- You're going home.
- I see.
People here are definitely different.
- That's Chungcheong Province.
- It's definitely different.
It's a different vibe.
The two older ones should sit.
- It's okay.
- Go ahead.
- I'm good here.
- Go on and sit.
- You have to sit so I can sit.
- You look unsteady.
No, I'm good.
- Sit down.
- Do you want to sit, Jae Myung?
Yes.
I really want to sit down.
He was really focused before.
Jae Myung wants to sit down.
- He really wants to sit down.
- My knees hurt.
(Since Jae Seok sat down, I will too.)
They didn't have that before.
Sun Bin, you said we were almost there,
- but we're going quite a while.
- Come on.
(It's been 10 minutes since she said they were almost there.)
"Arriving soon."
We are in Chungcheong Province.
- You said we were near...
- We're almost there.
Look. They sell walnut cakes.
That's Taegeukdang.
- Is that it?
- That's the original location?
- Yes, it is.
- Since 1957.
Wait. Should I get off and buy some?
- For Taegeukdang?
- Yes.
There's another one in Seongjeong-dong.
Wait. I should've dropped by.
- Those walnut cakes.
- The famous walnut cakes.
I'm crazy about walnut cakes.
- They're good with coffee.
- Yes.
You're right.
Are you talking about walnut cakes...
when we failed at the first spare time spot?
- Gosh.
- Right.
- We don't deserve to eat.
- Exactly.
Let's skip lunch, Jae Seok.
- We need to eat, though.
- We need to eat, right?
- Yes, we do.
- For the next game.
(Jae Myung does what Jae Seok says.)
That was the main branch.
(By the way...)
Sun Bin. Stop kidding and tell us how many stops are left.
I just pushed the button.
- How many stops are left?
- I'm serious.
- Are you telling the truth?
- Yes. We're really almost there.
- I'm starting to...
- Tell us in minutes.
- In minutes? Hold on.
- Is it going to take ten minutes?
- Where are we now?
- I can't stand it anymore.
Tell us if it'll take 30 minutes.
- It's...
- I've had enough, Sun Bin.
- Yes. We'll be there in 2 minutes.
- In 2 minutes?
The terminal will be there after we make a turn here.
- Okay.
- Yes. I'm serious.
This is when we say, "We're almost there" in Seoul.
- This is about it.
- We said that 30 minutes ago.
- It's been exactly 32 minutes.
- Come on, Jae Myung.
We're getting off now. We should get ready.
- Sure.
- For real?
- Yes. Get ready.
- It's the last stop.
- For real.
- Everyone will get off.
- Let's get off.
- Let's get off. I'm serious.
Which way?
- Many stores have disappeared.
- I remember filming downtown.
- The department store is huge.
- Yes.
Look at that sculpture.
- Look at the red bag.
- What is it?
- That's a landmark in Cheonan.
- Goodness.
Why is that a landmark?
- Is that a meeting point?
- That's right.
"Hey, come to the red bag."
- Exactly.
- That's it.
- There's always a meeting point.
- In every city.
- I see.
- Of course.
Wait. Hold on. Look.
The walnut cakes.
There are many walnut cake shops...
- on our way.
- Near here?
That's the main branch.
- Is walnut cake all he sees?
- Jae Seok.
Let's go buy some after lunch.
- You do love walnut cakes.
- Seriously. Yes.
We have to buy some.
They're not on break, are they?
- Gosh. Hello.
- Hello.
- Should we sit here?
- Do we just sit like this?
- Yes.
- This is interesting.
- Why?
(The variety-show rookie finds everything interesting.)
It's good.
- There's only one dish on the menu.
- What?
- Is there only one dish?
- Mulmakguksu.
Don't they have mulmakguksu?
- Do they only sell one dish?
- Yes.
There's only one dish.
- We'll get four.
- Yes.
- You don't serve broth, do you?
- No.
That's the only menu item.
We have to play a game to pay for lunch.
- Yes.
- That's right.
We're only having makguksu, though.
I have an idea, Jae Seok.
Should we include walnut cakes too?
(Should we add walnut cakes to the bet?)
- At once?
- You're obsessed with them.
From the granny's place we just saw?
- How long has he been on about it?
- Let's get a box each.
- In the middle...
- If he doesn't get one today,
he's going to cry.
We have to go to the shop for him.
You have to get some walnut cakes when you're in Cheonan.
When I came here to film last time,
I left without buying them.
- Come on. We have to try them.
- I just left.
- Hey, Jae Myung.
- Yes.
It's awkward to see you speak casually to Jae Myung.
- You'll get used to it.
- Of course.
I think it's because you didn't dye your hair black.
- Right. It's for work.
- Right.
I do look younger when I dye my hair black.
- Actually...
- Once I shave and all.
Actually, he's young,
- but the roles he has played...
- Yes.
- include a corporate mogul.
In the military setting,
- he'd be a two-star general.
- That's right.
- He'd be at least a two-star.
- Yes.
- The NIS director.
- The director of the NIS.
- And professors.
- He plays high-ranking positions.
Honestly, I look young, don't I?
- You do.
- Right?
- Compared to the roles you play.
- Exactly.
Some think I'm 60 years old.
Did you start out in theater?
I did theater in college. I was in the theater club.
I was based only in Busan.
And it's been 13 years since I started working in Seoul.
- It hasn't been long.
- No. I came when I was over 40.
(He left the Busan theater scene he was part of for 15 years...)
(and started from the bottom by taking numerous auditions.)
(Producer: Let's do this together.)
(Finally, the public started to respond to his performance.)
(He has established himself with his distinctive acting.)
(Yoo Jae Myung, the actor you can always count on)
I see. You used to...
- work only in Busan.
- Yes.
- Hey, it's here.
- It's here.
- Gosh. It smells amazing.
- Gosh. It looks good.
- This is...
- The sesame oil smells incredible.
This sesame oil is...
I've never tried this combination before.
- It has to be good.
- That's right.
- This combination.
- That's true.
This sauce.
It smells incredible.
(Slurping right away)
(Exclaiming)
- It's good, isn't it?
- Yes.
It's delicious.
- Is this perilla oil?
- Yes.
- Soy sauce and perilla oil.
- It's... Yes.
It's seasoned.
- It's a delicacy.
- It's good.
It tastes good.
(The noodle aficionado is satisfied too.)
You're a cool type.
You finished it already.
(A happy meal in Cheonan)
Goodness.
- As for the game, - Yes.
Should we play the bomb game?
What's that?
We'll set a timer.
We'll play the Word Chain while passing the phone around.
When the alarm goes off, that person has to pay.
- We don't know the set time.
- No, we don't.
You can go first, Jae Myung. Let's go this way.
- Okay.
- Okay. Good.
- I set the timer.
- Do we start right away?
- Yes.
- It's started.
- The Word Chain?
Yes. You can start now.
Makguksu.
- I think...
- Wednesday.
- Wednesday?
- Did you push the button?
Handcart.
- Garage.
- Gosh.
Tire.
- Fishcake.
- It's getting close.
- It might go off.
- Mukho.
- What?
- Tiger.
- Yes!
- What?
- Tiger.
- Yes!
It ended with him.
(The alarm went off as soon as he passed the phone.)
I had a hunch.
(Paying for lunch and walnut cakes at once)
- It's 30 walnut cakes.
- You're amazing, Jae Seok!
It will be 30 walnut cakes.
Jae Seok. I'll tell Mom...
you bought the walnut cakes for her.
You'll buy 30 walnut cakes.
"Honey, this is from Jae Seok."
(Laughing)
- We'll enjoy them.
- Good.
- That was close. I had a hunch.
- We'll enjoy them.
That's why he reached out his hand.
If I had passed it, it would've been Yeon Seok.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Thanks for the food, Jae Seok.
(Paying with Jae Seok Pay)
- You're amazing.
- I'm disappointed.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
Hope you do well.
Gosh. We should go get walnut cakes.
Gosh. Those walnut cakes.
Walnut cakes Jae Seok bought.
Yes.
I play Word Chain three times a day...
- because of my kid.
- Really? With your son. Right.
Yes. Because of my son.
I felt comfortable playing Word Chain.
- We should've played a harder one.
- I know.
- How old is he?
- He's eight.
- He's already 8.
- He's 8.
- When my son watches this, - Yes.
- he'll find it super hilarious.
- He'll love it.
- He'll ask to play the game.
- That's right.
(Smiling just thinking about his son)
I'm walking on air.
- Right?
- It does feel different.
Yeon Seok loves it when I have to pay.
We're in Cheonan.
I love it when he has to pay too.
- Yeon Seok.
- Should we get some coffee to go?
- Sounds good. Shall we do that?
- Coffee isn't included.
- Let's play another game.
Let's play another game and take coffee to go.
- For coffee...
- We have to play another game.
- Let's play another one.
- Are we playing a game again?
Why don't we simply play rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's do that.
- It's simple.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
No throw, you lose. Rock-paper-scissors.
(Scissors, scissors, scissors, rock)
Yes. The youngest always wins.
Sun Bin is in her hometown,
- and she's feeling great.
- She has Cheonan's energy.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- You were slow.
- I threw rock.
- You didn't throw anything.
- You didn't throw.
- I threw rock.
- You didn't.
- It was rock, Jae Myung.
If you didn't throw, it's over.
- No throw, you lose.
- Right.
- I said, "No throw, you lose."
- I had it here.
Let's cut him some slack since he paid for lunch.
No throw, you lose. Rock-paper-scissors.
Gosh. That was close.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Scissors, scissors, rock)
- Yes!
- It's...
- Jae Myung.
- Jae Seok.
Yeon Seok should pay.
- Yes.
- It's driving me crazy.
What's with you?
- Okay. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Win, lose)
- The older ones are buying today.
- Good.
- I'll buy the cold drinks.
- Great.
Others should get one too.
I'll get an iced Americano.
An iced Americano.
Do you prefer less ice?
Less... No, more ice will be fine.
- More ice. Just order it like that.
- I'll order it like this. Okay?
- Is it seven dollars?
- Pay.
- Is it only 7 dollars for 3 drinks?
(Feeling super happy)
I can't help but hum.
You feel great today.
I do. It's because you're paying.
You'll get ten walnut cakes.
Come on. Why?
- Because he's annoying?
- Yes. You'll get ten...
because you're annoying.
- Why?
- I can't stand you. You'll get ten.
Why?
- Enough is enough. You'll get ten.
- You can't do that.
- Yeon Seok gets ten walnut cakes.
- Jae Myung will get 30.
- Yes.
(Polite)
- He gets 30.
- He has a son.
- He has a kid.
- Don't discriminate.
- I don't discriminate.
- I need to...
I need to share them with my neighbors.
- And tell them he bought them.
- Yes. He has a kid.
(The drinks are ready already.)
Thank you. Have a good day.
By the way, they put so much ice.
They were serious when they said "more ice."
(More ice)
- Cheonan is...
- There's no room for the straw.
Cheonan people are so generous.
- Yes.
- Drink it as is.
Why did you choose "more ice?"
- It's...
- The ice is...
We don't need this many ice cubes.
- It's almost as if...
- This is...
How did it happen? Let's go now.
- The people in Cheonan...
- We can enjoy it cold.
- They're generous with their ice.
- Yes.
Let's run. Run.
Are we crossing at this light?
- Run.
- No.
Why is he so fast?
Run.
Hello.
- Are these free samples?
- Yes.
- An assorted...
- The medium has 30 walnut cakes.
Yes, you're right.
They cook them right in there.
Look at them.
- They're making them now.
- Then each cake costs...
- Okay.
- It's a total of eight boxes.
- It's 56 dollars.
- Okay.
Thank you, Jae Seok.
- No.
- Thank you.
- Pardon?
- Try this.
- Are they samples to try?
- Is this it?
- What is it?
- Yes, it is.
- They are free samples.
- Free samples? Oh, right.
They're fresh out of the oven.
Gosh. Then I need to try one.
(Putting it straight into his mouth)
I'll get 2 white bean paste ones and 2 red bean paste ones.
- Gosh.
- I'll pay separately.
- It's good.
- It's tasty.
- Gosh. The bean paste is good.
- Yes. It's delicious.
- A total of four boxes?
- Yes.
The bean paste tastes incredible.
Cheonan is all about walnut cakes.
- Sun Bin.
- Gosh.
Hello.
- Yes, thank you.
- Yes.
It's delicious. Awesome.
- It's good. It's warm.
- It tastes good.
It's very rich.
I'll get 2 white bean paste ones and 2 red bean paste ones.
I'll pay separately.
- It's good.
- It's tasty.
Gosh, Jae Seok.
There's a reason why it's good and famous.
- If he doesn't get walnut cakes...
- Gosh. I love it.
Cheonan is famous for its walnut cakes for a reason.
You got your wish.
Is the place near here?
We'll make a turn here.
It's from Lee Won Ho.
"As both family and colleagues,"
"we're creating flavors shaped by years of tradition."
"For my hero who has raised me,"
"please present her with a gift..."
"that could be remembered after 100 years."
- "My hero?"
- The family must be doing...
- Right.
- Do they cook together?
- Do they work together?
They create flavors.
They must be running a restaurant.
This is it. On the second floor.
(Does the second Whenever Guest create something together?)
We were right about this.
We were right.
- That's it. Over there.
- They sell dumpling stew.
I craved dumplings so much today.
(They go upstairs following the smell of dumplings.)
Is this it? Hello?
Did you send a letter to us?
- Yes.
- Lee Won Ho.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
You've come a long way. Sorry.
- We should've eaten lunch here.
- Welcome. Yes.
(Lee Won Ho, the second Whenever Guest)
Nice to meet you.
We didn't know it was a dumpling stew place.
(But where are the rest of his family?)
- Where do we go?
- Where should we sit?
The lunch hours are almost over.
- I see.
- Mother is resting upstairs.
- You can join her.
- She's upstairs.
- I'll take you upstairs. Let's go.
- Okay.
We can take the elevator.
- Go up one more floor?
- Yes.
Our house is on the fourth floor.
- You can go up there now.
- I see.
- Just with dumplings.
- They sell dumplings.
- They only sell dumplings.
- I really wanted to have them.
(The restaurant is on the 2nd floor.)
My mother lives on the fourth floor.
I live with my family on the fifth floor.
We live with my mother.
The three generations live together.
Literally, you live close to work with your family.
- Yes, you're right.
- Right.
That's awesome.
- This is our house.
- So this is your house.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Please come in.
- Gosh.
- Is this the living room?
Gosh. Hello.
Gosh. You run a restaurant...
while living upstairs over here.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
This is your real house.
Yes. It's a house.
It's...
Gosh. You've come all the way here. My goodness.
It's nothing. Thank you.
If we had known this was a dumpling stew place...
We would've come here.
I felt like eating dumplings today.
I took over her restaurant.
- We sell North Korean dumplings.
- Right.
My mother ran the restaurant for 27 years.
I'm her son, and I inherited it.
- It's been six years.
- Nice.
There aren't many places like this.
- No, there aren't.
- No.
- I did a lot of...
- I thought...
Are those dumplings?
She's preparing dumplings for you.
- Really?
- We should...
- try them at least.
- You should have some dumplings.
Gosh. They're dumplings with 40 years of history.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- The table is too small.
- Have some dumplings.
They already smell good.
(Warm)
Thank you.
It smells different. My goodness.
(Satisfied)
Our dumplings are known...
- for their light taste.
- It's tasty.
We chop and prepare the filling...
- from scratch.
- Gosh.
- Yes.
- Then it has to be good.
- The sauce is delicious too.
- Yes.
Even when a family makes dumplings for a living,
it's not that common...
for their children to inherit it...
and continue the tradition these days.
I thought of carrying on her business...
since I was young.
She got ill all of a sudden.
She battled colon cancer for a while.
She couldn't run the restaurant anymore.
We couldn't just close it...
- after running it for 27 years.
- That's true.
There were many regulars too.
So we couldn't close the restaurant.
I had worked as a chef for a long time too.
- Yes. I worked in Seoul.
- In what area of cooking?
I worked at Hotel S for 18 years.
- I cooked French cuisine.
- You cooked French cuisine.
- There's a French restaurant there.
- Yes.
I worked there for about 18 years.
(He received a presidential honor for his outstanding cooking skills.)
When I got the medal, I went to the Blue House.
They sent us a photo of me shaking hands with the president.
- When you got awarded.
- Yes.
- That's family treasure.
Since then, he had cooked in the Blue House.
- Nice.
- I didn't do it alone.
A team from Hotel S went there.
We went there every time the president had an event.
I met with all presidents.
Gosh. I see.
So I was working fine,
but since Mother got sick,
I thought I needed to live with her.
That was when I decided to do so.
Gosh. In this day and age,
that's not a matter of course.
You had your own job before.
How did you feel when he said he'd take over your restaurant?
I was a bit sad.
He studied a lot and had much experience.
He competed in WorldSkills,
and he was the first in Asia to win a medal.
(Understanding)
(Smiling)
He got a medal from the president.
Like I always say, parents tend...
to cherish the titles of their children.
They mention them so smoothly.
- It was as expected.
- It was expected.
So I was a little sad.
But he wanted to come and live with me.
So I said, "Okay. Let's live together."
And here we are now.
- Also, thankfully, - And...
he got the presidential medal.
- I told you.
- That was smooth.
That was very smooth.
She can't help mentioning it.
I just love it.
You love that the president awarded him.
- You love that the most.
- I do.
- He got awarded by the president.
- I'm proud of him.
I see. Every parent is the same.
Honestly,
- I heard it's really tough...
- Yes.
When you do business with your family.
- That's right.
- We argue all the time.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
We have disagreements every day.
In your mother's eyes,
there must be things she's not satisfied with.
You're right. She yelled at me all the time.
She isn't satisfied even if you tried so hard.
- I scolded him every day.
- Right.
You look like part of the family when you're sitting like that.
I have a bad knee right now.
- Exactly.
- I sat like a mother.
I thought he was part of the family.
- The three of them are a family.
- Like that.
- You made yourself comfortable.
- I know.
- You look very comfortable.
- Exactly.
I don't look like his father, do I?
- I don't look like his father?
- You look comfortable.
- They have similar smiles.
- I know.
- You could be his brother-in-law.
- Yes.
He's really good.
He's the son-in-law.
He's the older son-in-law.
He fits so naturally.
- That was very smooth.
- He's her oldest son-in-law.
Now, let's...
- Let's get it started.
- Yes.
- We have to nail it this time.
- We really have to.
- I know.
- Yes.
Okay.
What will the first present be?
"A mother and a son. We make dumplings together."
"And we sit next to each other to get some rest."
Two premium foot spas.
- Nice.
- Foot spas.
- You stand for a long time to work.
Two foot spas.
- There are two foot spas.
- I actually wanted...
to buy her one.
- That's good.
- We have one.
But it's an old model.
(Flick It into the Steamer)
(Flick table tennis balls into a steamer.)
(Round 1: Get 2 out of 10 balls into the steamer.)
(Time limit: 30 seconds)
Do we flick the ball?
What? Do we flick it?
It's a dumpling steamer.
(They have to flick a ball on the steamer.)
It'll be on the steamer.
So it's a bit different...
- from what we used to do.
- Gosh. That's not it.
We were too good at it.
- We were so good at it.
- I thought...
we should throw the ball.
- Do you want us to flick it?
- We're masters at it now.
(It goes in even when he throws it casually.)
- We've become masters.
- You're right.
I need to try it a couple of times and get the hang of it.
We have a long table because three generations live together.
- Yes. I see that.
- I see.
- That's why.
- Usually, six people sit at a time.
- This is a table for ten.
- Yes.
(Jae Seok is the first one to practice.)
- Gosh. It doesn't go in.
- It depends on how it gets bounced.
We should let it bounce like this.
- Gosh. This is hard.
- We have to try a few times.
- I don't get it.
- We used to throw and bounce it.
- They won't let us do it easily.
- What?
It's tough.
In short, they won't let us...
The ball has to bounce around here.
- develop some skills.
- Like that.
(Going in)
Can we try it multiple times?
- Gosh. It's hard.
- It's hard.
What now? It's so hard.
We have to make it happen here.
- They're truly amazing.
- We have to make it happen here.
We have to pull it off no matter what.
I need to get the direction right.
We only need to score two goals.
I think this one is better than the game we played before.
The direction is the key.
- Let's try it.
- Let's do it.
(They go for it quickly.)
- Okay.
- Ten balls? Then we can do it.
We're going to make our first try.
- Let's cheer up.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3, - Let's go.
- let's go.
- Let's go.
We have six seconds each.
- Do I get three balls?
- Yes.
Three, two, two, and three.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Say, "Here we go."
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(1st try)
- That's it. Gosh. That was close.
- I should flick it weaker.
- That's it.
- What?
- There you go.
(A clean start for the first player, Yeon Seok)
One more goal. I think we'll pull it off.
I think it'll work.
Go in.
- You have to flick it stronger.
- We're running out of time.
Flick it stronger.
That's it. No. Flick it stronger.
You have ten seconds.
Ten seconds.
(They just need to put in one more ball.)
You have three balls. You're good. You can do it.
It will go in.
- Just get the direction right.
- Five, four,
- That's it.
- three, two,
one.
Include this one!
That's it.
- One.
- That's it.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
I flicked it sideways.
(They failed their first try.)
- How could no one pull it off?
- No, I think we'll pull it off.
- It will work.
- Get the direction right.
- Do I go last?
- You go last.
- Okay.
- Will you go first, Jae Myung?
- Yes. I'll try with two balls.
- Finish it before it reaches me.
Finish it before it reaches me.
- Just finish it.
- We'll be quick this time.
Yes. Just finish it off.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Do it.
- Say, "Here we go."
Okay. Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(2nd try)
- That was close.
- That was so close.
- That's it. Gosh.
- Goodness.
It's not easy.
- I think she'll put one in.
- I think you can make it.
Just one.
Why can't I do it?
- I flicked it too hard.
- It was too strong.
(2nd try)
Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok, put one in.
- One...
- That's it.
- Gosh.
One...
- Gosh. It's so hard.
- You have ten seconds.
- Just 1.
- We only have 10 seconds?
- Just put one in.
- We have to be quicker.
Gosh. I just wanted one to go in.
(Ace Yeon Seok is the only one left.)
- Five, four, - There you go.
- three, two, - That's it.
One.
(They failed their second try.)
(Pulling her hair out)
Good job. You did well.
Good job. Yes.
She's so supportive, which makes me feel even worse.
I feel even worse because she's so supportive.
(Trying hard not to look at her)
- What now?
- It's okay.
- Don't be discouraged.
- You flick three balls.
(Staring)
- I'll try it with three balls.
- Yes.
- Okay. Try flicking 3 balls.
- I'll go 1st.
I got the hang of it, except for the weak bounce.
- Yes? It's in the right direction.
- Darn it.
It's on the right track, except for how weak the bounce is.
- Jae Seok, you can go last.
- This is it, except...
- This is it.
- We feel pressed for time.
- This is it, but the bounce is...
- I'll go last.
- For goodness' sake.
- The bounce is...
We have to pull it off this time.
- Flick it a little harder.
- We have to make it this time.
- We really have to pull it off.
- This is it.
- Let's go.
- Who will go first?
- I'll go first.
- Jae Myung will.
- Jae Myung will go 1st.
- I'll go 2nd.
- You'll go second.
- Go!
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- Go.
- Calm down.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
- Set.
- Here I go.
(4th try)
That's it. Darn it.
I think it'll go in.
- That's it. Come on. Why?
- Flick it a bit harder.
(Sighing)
(He's out without scoring any goals.)
It'll happen. It's going to work this time.
We'll succeed.
- We'll succeed this time.
- It's driving me nuts.
- It's going to work. But why...
- Let's finish it off.
Go, Jae Seok.
Let's go.
Darn it.
Ten seconds.
That's it.
- He did it.
- Wait. Just 1 more.
- Just 1 more.
(They'll complete Round 1 if they make 1 more goal.)
- Just one more.
- Five,
- four, three, - There you go. Just one more.
- two, one.
- Just one more.
(He flicks the last ball with 1 second left.)
- Just one.
- One.
That's it!
One.
(It went in!)
(Yoo One Shot has finished it!)
(Screaming)
You have to count that one in.
- It was a buzzer-beater.
- A buzzer-beater. Yes.
One.
(The ball left with 1 second left.)
That's it!
(And it went in the steamer with a whistle.)
(Round 1, success!)
It was truly dramatic.
(Yeon Seok's miraculous buzzer-beater)
That was tough.
(They won the Round 1 presents, 2 premium foot spas.)
- Hey, that was...
- He beat the buzzer.
- It left the starting point.
- Gosh.
- It left.
- Yes.
Five, six, seven, eight, nine, and ten.
We have six more tries.
Okay. Decide whether you'll go on or stop.
What do you want to do, Mother?
Go on. Why not?
Go!
- They'll go for Round Two.
- They can go for it for now.
It's hard.
- It was...
- My legs are shaky.
- I think I have an upset stomach.
- It's nervous to watch too.
It's extremely stressful.
"In place of the apron I hand over to my son,"
"I'll wrap around my neck with a premium scarf."
(Round 2 present: A scarf from a designer brand)
We haven't had a designer item for a long time.
- Yes. It's a premium scarf.
- I couldn't even buy it for her.
- It's a designer scarf for Mother.
- Yes.
(Beaming)
(Round 2)
(The steamer will be closed up.)
- The opening gets smaller.
- I see.
- On the contrary...
They even use a ruler to close it.
- I can't believe it.
- Now,
- we have to bounce it higher.
- That's right.
They have to be exact.
- You're too tight.
- It won't get out once it gets in.
I think we should end it...
- in Round 2, not Round 3.
- Just do it haphazardly.
Gosh. I'm nervous again.
(It doesn't look easy even to our ace, Yeon Seok.)
- It'll go in.
- I know.
- Let's go for it.
- Yes.
- Do it.
- You can try three balls.
- Let's go.
- I'll do it.
- Go, Yeon Seok.
- Here we go.
Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
Go!
(5th try)
That's it.
- Again.
- There you go.
Again.
- That's it.
- Gosh.
Keep going right away.
- He misaligned it.
- Good.
Keep going right away.
- He misaligned it.
- Good.
Do it with confidence. Good.
- Now.
- Good.
I was scared because I thought it was my turn.
- You're on point.
- You have ten seconds left.
- It has to bounce higher.
- Put it higher up in the air.
- Gosh.
- It has to go higher.
- Five, four, - You can do it.
- three...
- That's it.
- Three...
(It's a goal!)
You did it.
(He did it!)
That's it.
(Amazed)
That was so quick.
(They won the Round 2's designer scarf.)
It went quickly.
Hold on.
- We have some tries left, though.
- Round Three is...
- Okay, then.
- We're in trouble.
- Six, seven, eight, nine...
- We have five more tries, right?
We have five more tries.
We have five more tries and a chance.
- We're in a similar situation.
- It'll get harder...
- Why is this happening?
- with a better present.
You already got a scarf from a designer brand.
Exactly.
- Please think carefully about it.
- Yes.
Please talk to each other.
- You can stop. You can go on.
- Okay.
Go on and talk to each other.
- Should we stop now?
- When we fail after five tries,
- the scarf and foot spas...
- Do we have five tries left?
- will disappear.
- Five tries.
- We have a chance too.
- We do have many tries, though.
I think we'll pull it off.
- We do have many tries left.
- I think we can do this one.
- I think we'll pull it off.
- It's not that bad.
But we don't know how many goals we have to make.
I think Jae Seok will pull it off.
- We can do it this time.
- I think he got the hang of it.
- Have you made up your mind?
- Yes.
Okay. One, two, three.
(What will be the Whenever Guest's choice?)
- Do you want to go for it?
- Go.
- Okay. We'll continue.
- Yes.
Since they'll go for it...
- Now...
- In that case...
"Give some rest to the muscles..."
"that have been tensed up in the strict kitchen."
- "A massage chair."
- A massage chair.
- Goodness.
- A massage chair?
(Round 3 present: A massage chair)
- It's really big.
- It's huge. What do we do?
- That's an expensive one.
- The massage chair.
- Gosh!
- Gosh, I would love to get that.
- That's expensive.
- Gosh.
- That's really expensive.
- I was planning to...
remove that sofa...
to place one of those.
The massage chair is perfect.
- Gosh.
- Right.
- We have to make it, though.
- All right. It's Round Three.
- Gosh, hold on.
- We can't lose everything.
(Round 3)
(The steamer will be placed further away.)
It will be placed further away? That might be better for us.
- That might be better for us.
- Our shots went too far earlier.
Instead of getting smaller,
- that's better for us.
- Right.
- That's better for us.
- Yes.
Setting the right direction will be really important.
- That's better for us.
- Right.
- Yes.
Setting the right direction will be really important.
- I think that's better.
- The direction will be important.
- I agree.
- The direction.
- Nice!
- Yes!
- We got it!
- Today is the day!
- Nice.
- Today feels like our lucky day.
Right.
- Would you like to go first?
- There you go.
Nice!
- Nice!
- There you go.
Okay!
Sun Bin got the hang of it.
- What would you like to do?
- I'll go first, then.
I'll just go for it.
- I think you will make it.
- Right.
(I think you will make it.)
- Let's go!
- Here we go!
- Here I go!
- Ready.
- Yes!
- We got it!
- Today is the day!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
Set.
What are you doing? Get to your senses.
Focus.
- Well, - I'm awful at this.
- you feel nervous...
- I can't do it once.
- during the challenge.
- It's more to the right.
- You feel nervous...
- I can't do it once.
- during the challenge.
- It's more to the right.
- It's in! Gosh.
- It was the right direction.
- Just one.
- One, two! Go in!
- Gosh!
(6th try)
End it here.
- Just one!
- One!
- Just put in one.
- It's in!
Yes!
- Let's end it here.
- Ten seconds left.
- It's in!
- It's over!
(It's over!)
- It's in!
- It's over!
(Will they pass Round 3 like this?)
- Ten seconds left.
- One more time!
- It's in!
- It's over!
(6th try)
(It went in...)
(and bounced back out.)
- Gosh!
(6th try)
Five, four, three,
two, one.
It's in!
(They failed their sixth try.)
- It bounced back out!
- This looks possible!
- Right.
- Please!
- This is driving me crazy.
- Good job.
- We were almost there.
- Right.
- Gosh.
- Should we use the chance now?
- Now?
- We should use the chance now.
That sounds good. We'll use the chance now.
Gosh, that was close.
- That was so close.
- We were almost there.
There's one bad choice.
The other four are good.
(What will be picked with the quick use of the chance?)
Try opening it.
- It's a good one!
- "The ace..."
"The ace will go alone for this try."
- What?
- Alone?
Alone?
- The ace will go alone?
- Right.
Choose one ace for us.
(The ace will use 10 table tennis balls alone.)
- Gosh.
- That person will use ten balls.
I believe these two are the strongest candidates.
- Gosh, I want to be an ace too.
- It will be him.
- Yeon Seok!
- Right.
- Let's go!
- Do it calmly.
- Show us what you've got.
- Let's go!
- Don't rush yourself.
Do it calmly. You have enough time.
I think you can take it slow.
- Should I place the next one?
- That sounds great.
- I'll practice.
I'll take around two shots.
You're using the time all by yourself. Take it slow.
Take it slow.
- Let's go!
- Bam!
- This is what it's like.
- Let's go!
- Right.
- Gosh!
- Let's go!
- Bam!
- This is it.
- Let's go!
This is it.
It'll be different from practice.
- I'll go for it.
- I'll place it for you.
- Let's go!
Let's go!
- Let's do a cheer.
- Let's go!
- One, two, three.
- All right.
- You have enough time.
- Okay.
- This is the eighth try.
- All right.
- You have enough time.
Right.
- All right.
- Call it out.
- Are you ready?
- Take a deep breath.
Focus.
- Here I go!
- Ready.
- Do it calmly.
- Set.
- There you go.
- Gosh!
- Take it slow.
- You still have time.
- You have enough time.
- Right.
You have enough time.
- It should be more to the side.
- Oh, gosh.
- You have enough time.
- I'm getting nervous.
- Don't get nervous.
- Gosh! You still have many left.
- You have enough time.
There you go.
Gosh, that was close.
- I have to put in one now.
- It will go in.
- You have enough time.
- Let's go!
- I have to put it in!
You have enough time.
- Let's go!
- There you go.
- Gosh!
- You have enough time.
(Chance round, 8th try)
There you go.
(There you go.)
- Gosh!
Let's go!
(There are only 2 balls left.)
- It's in.
- Five,
- four, three, - Just one!
Two...
(They end up failing with their eighth try after using the chance.)
- It's okay.
- Good try.
- This isn't easy.
- Right.
- Right. Good try.
- This is... Gosh.
- How can this happen?
- This is really hard.
- This is hard.
Your aim gets thrown off as you feel the pressure.
It's hard. It isn't easy to do.
- We have two tries left.
- Right.
- He used ten balls alone.
That isn't easy to do.
- How many tries do we have left?
- We have two tries left.
We have our 9th and 10th tries left. That's 2.
- We only have two tries left.
- Hold on.
I think this is a bit off.
- You should...
- Well,
I'm just trying to place it nicely.
- You should pour some water.
- Right.
- Let's do this.
- I want to return to Seoul...
with a smile.
- Let's go!
- Let's make it happen.
- Let's think this is the last try.
- Right.
- We have to do that.
What am I doing?
- It's going to work out.
- We have two tries left.
- Let's go for it.
- Shall we start?
- Let's go!
- You guys can finish this!
- You can do it!
- Who will go first?
- Here we go!
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
(9th try)
- Gosh!
(It hit the side again.)
Go in!
(9th try)
Good try!
Go in!
(9th try)
Gosh!
- At least one!
- Gosh, that was weak.
It will go in this time, right?
Gosh!
(It bounced back out again.)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy!
I can't believe it.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Ten seconds left.
I can't believe it.
- It will go in this time.
- Get ready.
- He did it!
- Okay!
- This one will go in as well.
- Four,
- There we go. Go.
- Just one, Sun Bin!
- Sun Bin!
- Don't rush it.
- Go in!
- One.
Sun Bin!
- She did it!
- Go in!
- One.
- No.
- She did it!
She did it!
(They fail after it hits the side.)
- Gosh!
- That was close!
- Sun Bin did so well!
- Good try!
- That was a great shot.
- Good try.
- I should've put in at least one.
- It's our last try.
- Good try.
Right.
- It's our last try.
- Good try.
Should we go with the same order?
- It's our last try.
- The same order.
We'll do our best for the last try.
- Right.
- All right.
- That was a good try.
- I'll give you some energy!
- One, two, three.
- Let's go!
- All right.
- Please!
That was a good try.
(They ended up reaching their last try.)
Sun Bin should take the final shot.
- Okay.
- Right.
The final shot.
Gosh, the direction was off.
- All right. Let's do this.
- It was too low.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
Good try.
- Gosh, I feel sick.
- We have to do this.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
- This is the last try.
- Right.
Let's go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
All right. Here we go!
- Ready. Set.
- Please!
(Last try)
Go!
- It's too much to the left.
- It will go in.
One more time!
- Gosh!
Let's go!
(Last try)
Gosh! One more time! Let's go!
It will go in.
- Gosh, it didn't go in.
- That was close.
Gosh! That was close.
- Ten seconds left.
- One more time!
(Last try)
It went in!
(One ball goes in.)
One more time! This will go in! Gosh!
- Five, - One more time!
Four,
- three, two...
- Don't rush it!
- Sun Bin!
Don't rush it!
One.
(The last ball)
(It went in!)
It went in!
(The ball bounced off the edge.)
(Screaming)
Good try!
(It's over.)
That was so close.
You did your best!
It's okay!
(The prizes get taken back.)
Well done!
- Gosh, I should've put in one.
- Bye!
- I should've put in 1.
- I should've put in one.
- You did your best!
- It's okay.
- We're so sorry.
You did your best!
You cheered for us so much.
- We're so sorry.
- You did your best!
Gosh, it's fine!
It's okay. You tried your best.
- I should've put in one.
- You did your best!
- Sun Bin's shot was so close.
- I'm still happy.
- Sun Bin's shot was so good.
- Sorry?
- Gosh!
- Well done!
I should've put in one at the start.
- Gosh.
- That's all that matters.
- That was so close.
- I should be grateful...
- for having all of you here.
- Gosh,
- this is so disappointing.
- I feel so bad.
I'm very sorry.
- Thank you.
- Sorry.
- We still get presents.
- Right.
Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Well,
I'll buy you the scarf.
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh, it's fine.
The Daughter of Cheonan apologizes to you.
- The Daughter of Cheonan.
- I feel so happy today.
Sun Bin and Jae Myung's...
- movie...
- Right.
- is about to be released.
- "Ugly Duckling Ms. Maeng."
- Right.
- Become a big hit!
- We hope it becomes a big hit!
- Thank you.
- We will make sure to watch it!
They make the best reactions.
- Right.
- I feel so bad.
Don't feel bad!